Standing side flexions with the weights by side.
An exercise for an area right here in the middle section of your body.
You're going to stand up tall, and I want to show you from the side that your hips are going to be tucked in, and your belly is going to be in.
Without letting the shoulders hump like this.
So you really want to keep it tall and just like if you're looking into your zipper right here you're going to tuck those hips.
Okay, your knees are going to be slightly bent as you do that.
So when you keep your weights by the side make sure that you're also keeping your chest tall by squeezing your back muscles, bringing the shoulders down by using the back.
Keeping your feet under your hips, parallel, bending the knees a little bit with the tuck in vacuuming your tummy.
You're going to take an inhale and reach with the weight, exhale coming up.
Make sure that your head follows the line of the spine, meaning the head is going to want to do this.
And you see that this alignment right here.
So you want to keep the line going up all the way to the crown of the head.
Exhale.
Inhale.
Do a few, make sure you do same number on one side and the other, and you'll have good looking core before you know it.
See you soon.